// data file 

const questionsData = [
  {question: "Good morning! How are you feeling this morning?",
  answer: ["happy", "tired", "melancholy", "relaxed"]
  },
  {question: "Now that you're awake, what are you going to do?",
  answer: ["Go back to bed", "Have some breakfast", "Take a long shower", "Get some exercising in"]
  },
  {question: "What drink do you need to get you going?",
  answer: ["Coffee and more coffee", "Tea for me", "Water. Gotta keep hydrated", "Zevia"]
  },
  {question: "How are you spending the morning?",
  answer: ["Time to work", "Going for a bike, run or walk", "Running some errands", "Relaxing at home"]
  },
  
  {question: "Time for lunch already! Which sounds the most appealing to you?",
  answer: ["No time! Grab something quick", "Whip something up at home", "Pick up something from the organic grocery store", "A nice lunch in a cafe"]
  },
  {question: "You've got the afternoon free! What will you get up to?",
  answer: ["Read a book under a tree", "Go catch a movie", "Maybe go rock-climbing or for a hike", "See where my feet take me"]
  },
  {question: "Are you spending the afternoon alone or with others?",
  answer: ["With one or two others", "It's me time", "Getting a big group together", "Hanging with my pet"]
  },
  {question: "Where would you rather eat dinner?",
  answer: ["At home", "My favourite restaurant", "Someplace new and fancy", "On a patio or in a park"]
  },
  {question: "How are you spending the rest of your evening?",
  answer: ["Watch the sun set with my favourite beverage", "Go out dancing", "Play some boardgames with friends", " Visit an art gallery"]
  },
  {question: "Yawn! Time for bed. What's your night-time routine?",
  answer: ["Do some yoga or meditation to wind down", "Finish watching that show on Netflix", "Scroll through social media", "Write in my journal"]
  }
]

export default questionsData;